A Register of the Stephen J. Tonsor Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1946-1998 and undated.
  - Goodman, George D., 1969 (Folder 9: 47)
  - Goodrich, Pierre F., 1965-1971 (Folder 9: 48)
  - Gordus, Adon A., 1969 (Folder 9: 49)
  - Gospodinoff, Gospodin, 1979 (Folder 9: 50)
  - Goss, Steven G., 1968-1969 (Folder 9: 51)
  - Gottfried, Paul E., 1970-1994 and undated (Folder 9: 52)
  - Grady, Susanna, 1993 (Folder 9: 53)
  - Graf, Otto, 1967 (Folder 9: 54)
  - Graham, George J., Jr., 1978 (Folder 9: 55)
  - Graham, Theodora R., 1985 (Folder 9: 56)
  - Greeley, Andrew M., 1975-1976 (Folder 9: 57)
  - Green, Richard, undated (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - Green, Shirley, 1966 (Folder 10: 2)
  - Green, Willard P., 1974 (Folder 10: 3)
  - Greenbaum, Louis S., 1970 (Folder 10: 4)
  - Greenberg, Janelle, 1982 (Folder 10: 5)
  - Greenberg, Mark, 1981 (Folder 10: 6)
  - Greenberger, Allen J., 1970 (Folder 10: 7)
  - Greene, Amy, 1971 (Folder 10: 8)
  - Greenfield, James L., 1965 (Folder 10: 9)
  - Greenleaf, Charles W., 1974 (Folder 10: 10)
  - Greenstein, Steve, 1966 (Folder 10: 11)
  - Greenwood, Mary L., 1983 and undated (Folder 10: 12)
  - Greifer, Jojn K., undated (Folder 10: 13)
  - Grew, Raymond, 1971 (Folder 10: 14)
  - Griffin, Bryan, 1981 (Folder 10: 15)
  - Griffin, F. Glenn, 1982 (Folder 10: 16)
  - Griffin, Robert P., 1967-1969 (Folder 10: 17)
  - Grimes, Wellington V., 1970 (Folder 10: 18)
  - Grix, John C., 1971 (Folder 10: 19)
  - GrüBen, Mit den besten, 1991 (Folder 10: 20)
  - Gueguen, John A., 1971-1984 (Folder 10: 21)
  - Guenin, Jon, 1985 (Folder 10: 22)
  - Guirard, Jim, 1986 (Folder 10: 23)
  - Gullander, W. P., 1964 (Folder 10: 24)
  - Gum, William L., 1962 (Folder 10: 25)
  - Gupta, Brijen K., 1970 (Folder 10: 26)
  - Guth, Lloyd, 1969 (Folder 10: 27)
  - Guthrie, John C., 1969 (Folder 10: 28)
  - Gutman, Sanford, 1967-1971 (Folder 10: 29)
  - Guy, Fred, 1986 (Folder 10: 30)
  - Haag, Ernest Van Den, 1968-1979 (Folder 10: 31)
  - Haag, John J., 1967 (Folder 10: 32)
  - Haas, John M., 1992 (Folder 10: 33)
  - Haas, Karen, 1970 (Folder 10: 34)
  - Habeck, Noel, undated (Folder 10: 35)
  - Haber, William, 1969-1971 (Folder 10: 36)
  - Haberer, Joseph, 1971 (Folder 10: 37)
  - Habler(?), Martin, 1989 (Folder 10: 38)
  - Hackett, George O., 1970 (Folder 10: 39)
  - Hackett, William H. Y., Jr., 1967 (Folder 10: 40)
  - Hagy, James, 1984 (Folder 10: 41)
  - Hales, Daniel B., 1979 (Folder 10: 42)
  - Hall,(?), 1989 (Folder 10: 43)
  - Hall, Jason Y., 1975-1984 (Folder 10: 44)
  - Hall, Terry R., 1982-1987 (Folder 10: 45)
  - Halperin, S. William, 1970 (Folder 10: 46)
  - Hamburger, Joseph, 1974 (Folder 10: 47)
  - Hamilton, Lee, 1966-1974 (Folder 10: 48)
  - Hanseek(?), Bob, 1983 (Folder 10: 49)
  - Hansen, Kenneth N., 1983 (Folder 10: 50)
  - Harcourt, Brace and World, Inc., 1966 (Folder 10: 51)
  - Harms, George W., 1970 (Folder 10: 52)
  - Harper, F. A., 1967-1971 (Folder 10: 53)
  - Harrell, Kenneth E., 1970 (Folder 10: 54)
  - Harrigan, Anthony H., 1979-1982 (Folder 10: 55)
  - Harrington, Joel F., 1981-1984 (Folder 10: 56)
  - Harris, Cynthia, undated (Folder 10: 57)
  - Harris, Ralph, 1970-1975 (Folder 10: 58)
  - Harriss, C. Lowell, 1969 (Folder 10: 59)
  - Hart, Donald J., 1970 (Folder 10: 60)
  - Hartman, John D., 1971 (Folder 10: 61)
  - Hartwell, Max, 1984 (Folder 10: 62)
  - Hastings College of Law, 1970 (Folder 10: 63)
  - Hatcher, Harlan, 1967 (Folder 10: 64)
  - Havard, William C., 1978 (Folder 10: 65)
  - Hay, G. E., 1971-1974 (Folder 10: 66)
  - Hayek, Frederich A. von, 1980 (Folder 10: 67)
  - Hays, William L., 1966-1969 (Folder 10: 68)
  - Haywood, C. Robert, 1967 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Headden, W. P., 1966 (Folder 11: 2)
  - Headley, John M., 1986 (Folder 11: 3)
  - Heatherly, Charles L., 1971 (Folder 11: 4)
  - Hegeler Institute, 1971 (Folder 11: 5)
  - Heggoy, Alf A., 1986 (Folder 11: 6)
  - Heise, Herman A., 1969 (Folder 11: 7)
  - Heldt, Carl A., 1970 (Folder 11: 8)
  - Hellerich, Mahlon H., 1970-1971 (Folder 11: 9)
  - Henrie, Mark C., 1987 (Folder 11: 10)
  - Henry, Michael, 1986-1988 (Folder 11: 11)
  - Herberg, Will, 1969 (Folder 11: 12)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1981-1986 (Folder 11: 13)
  - Herlihy, David, 1971 (Folder 11: 14)
  - Hermalin, Jolene, 1981 (Folder 11: 15)
  - Herman, Beaumont S., 1970 (Folder 11: 16)
  - Herman, Martin M., undated (Folder 11: 17)
  - Hesburgh, Theodore M., 1968 (Folder 11: 18)
  - Hessen, Robert, 1973 (Folder 11: 19)
  - Hewitt, Bill, undated (Folder 11: 20)
  - Heyck, T. W., 1975 (Folder 11: 21)
  - Heywood, C. William, 1970 (Folder 11: 22)
  - Hibbs, Virginia G., 1975 (Folder 11: 23)
  - Higham, John, 1995 (Folder 11: 24)
  - Hill, W. W., 1990-1993 (Folder 11: 25)
  - Hill, Watts, Jr., 1969 (Folder 11: 26)
  - Hirsch, Eric D., Sr., 1970 (Folder 11: 27)
  - Historian, 1976 (Folder 11: 28)
  - Hoab, Eric G., undated (Folder 11: 29)
  - Hobbs, Walter C., 1992 (Folder 11: 30)
  - Hochberg, Leonard, 1993 (Folder 11: 31)
  - Hoffer, Kenneth, 1967-1972 (Folder 11: 32)
  - Hofman, Amos, 1981 (Folder 11: 33)
  - Holland, James C., 1986 (Folder 11: 34)
  - Hollwig, James M., 1988 (Folder 11: 35)
  - Holt, Andrew W., 1984 (Folder 11: 36)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1966 (Folder 11: 37)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1985 (Folder 11: 38)
  - Hollis and Carter, 1951 (Folder 11: 39)
  - Hollister, C. Warren, 1984 (Folder 11: 40)
  - Hollingsworth, J. Rogers, 1971 (Folder 11: 41)
  - Holthoon, Frederick L. Van, 1987-1992 and undated (Folder 11: 42)
  - Hoover Institution, 1967-1992 and undated (Folder 11: 43-44)
  - Hope College, 1981 (Folder 11: 45)
  - Hopkins, Richard J., 1987 (Folder 11: 46)
  - Hornback, Bert G., 1979-1992 (Folder 11: 47)
  - Horowitz, Irving Louis, 1973 (Folder 11: 48)
  - Horowitz, Robert, 1969-1971 (Folder 11: 49)
  - Horsch, William F., 1969 (Folder 11: 50)
  - Horten, Alphons and Elisabeth, 1973-1974 (Folder 11: 51)
  - Houghton, Donald A., 1970 (Folder 11: 52)
  - Houseck, Bob, 1983-1990 and undated (Folder 11: 53)
  - Howami(?), George F., 1968 (Folder 11: 54)
  - Howard, John A., 1966-1996 and undated (Folder 11: 55)
  - Howell, Martha C., 1986-1987 (Folder 11: 56)
  - Hoxie, R. Gordon, 1974 (Folder 11: 57)
  - Huber, Rober J., 1970 (Folder 11: 58)
  - Hughes, Clarence, 1972 (Folder 11: 59)
  - Hughes, Joseph D., 1970 (Folder 11: 60)
  - Humboldt-Stiftung, Alexander von, 1971 (Folder 11: 61)
  - Humphrey, Hubert, 1968 (Folder 11: 62)
  - Hunter, Timothy N., 1974 and undated (Folder 11: 63)
  - Hurtig, Serge, 1981 (Box-folder 12: 1)
  - Hussman, Cindy L., 1981 (Folder 12: 2)
  - Husted, Ralph W., 1987-1991 (Folder 12: 3)
  - Huston(?), Joe, 1971 (Folder 12: 4)
  - Hutson, Charles, 1970 (Folder 12: 5)
  - Hutt, William H., 1980. (Folder 12: 6)
    See also Hoover Institution
  - Hyde, John M., 1983 (Folder 12: 7)
  - Idzarda, Stanley J., 1965 (Folder 12: 8)
  - Idziak, Janine Marie, 1975 (Folder 12: 9)
  - Iggers, Georg G., 1966-1970 (Folder 12: 10)
  - Iklé, Frank W., 1971 (Folder 12: 11)
  - Illinois State University, 1964-1971 (Folder 12: 12)
  - Imesch, Joseph L., 1967 (Folder 12: 13)
  - Indiana State University, 1981 (Folder 12: 14)
  - Indiana University, 1975-1981 (Folder 12: 15)
  - Institute for Public Affairs Research, 1970 (Folder 12: 16)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc., 1960-1986. (Folder 12: 17)
    See also John F. Lulves, Jr., E. Victor Milione, and G. R. Watts
  - Isaac, Erich, 1971 (Folder 12: 18)
  - Ishida, Nakao, 1957 (Folder 12: 19)
  - Iverson, Irving L., 1969 (Folder 12: 20)
  - Ives, C. P., 1966-1975 and undated (Folder 12: 21)
  - Jackson, Hal P., 1967 (Folder 12: 22)
  - Jackson Henry M., 1957 (Folder 12: 23)
  - Jacobson, Jon S., 1988 (Folder 12: 24)
  - Jaffa, Harry V, 1970 (Folder 12: 25)
  - James, C. H., 1970 (Folder 12: 26)
  - Jarrett, Mary H., 1981-1985 (Folder 12: 27)
  - Jeffrey, Julie, 1982 (Folder 12: 28)
  - Jellema, William W., 1967-1970 (Folder 12: 29)
  - Jellison, Richard, 1985 (Folder 12: 30)
  - Jensen, Dwight, circa 1970 (Folder 12: 31)
  - Jensen, Ken, 1983 (Folder 12: 32)
  - Jewell, Harry, 1974 (Folder 12: 33)
  - Johns, Kingston, 1970 (Folder 12: 34)
  - Johns, Michael, 1986 (Folder 12: 35)
  - Johnson, Bruce Alan, 1973 (Folder 12: 36)
  - Johnson, Harold K., 1969 (Folder 12: 37)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963 (Folder 12: 38)
  - Johnson, Sandra R., 1965 (Folder 12: 39)
  - Jones, C. Clyde, 1958 (Folder 12: 40)
  - Jones, Charles F., 1969 (Folder 12: 41)
  - Jones, Christy E., 1983 (Folder 12: 42)
  - Jones, Gary L., 1975-1976 (Folder 12: 43)
  - Jones, Jean, 1986 (Folder 12: 44)
  - Jones, Michael, 1984 (Folder 12: 45)
  - Jones, Owen, 1986 (Folder 12: 46)
  - Jordan, David, 1966-1967 (Folder 12: 47)
  - Joy, Daniel F., 1971 (Folder 12: 48)
  - Joyce, Michael S., 1986 (Folder 12: 49)
  - Joyner, Quintard, 1981-1986 (Folder 12: 50)
  - Judd, Thomas W., 1986 (Folder 12: 51)
  - Judge, Richard D., Mrs., 1968 (Folder 12: 52)
  - Julber, Eric, 1968 and undated (Folder 12: 53)
  - Kalish, Abraham H., 1970 (Folder 12: 54)
  - Kaplan, Roger, 1985 (Folder 12: 55)
  - Kapp, Ronald O., 1974 (Folder 12: 56)
  - Keating, Michael, undated (Folder 12: 57)
  - Keckeissen, Joseph E., 1975 (Folder 12: 58)
  - Kelley, Margaret "Maryland,", 1975 (Folder 12: 59)
  - Kelly, Alfred H., 1961 (Folder 12: 60)
  - Kemmerer, Donald L., undated (Folder 12: 61)
  - Kemp, Arthur, 1962-1975 (Folder 12: 62)
  - Kenna, E. Douglas, 1974 (Folder 12: 63)
  - Kennard, John B., Jr., 1976 (Folder 12: 64)
  - Kennedy, Dane, 1986 (Folder 12: 65)
  - Kennedy, David B., 1969-1994 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - Kennedy, James A., 1967-1969 (Folder 13: 2)
  - Kenyon College, 1973 (Folder 13: 3)
  - Kerman, David V., 1966-1971 (Folder 13: 4)
  - Kern, Paul J., 1970-1974 (Folder 13: 5)
  - Kernan, Peter J., 1969-1970 (Folder 13: 6)
  - Kershner, Howard E., 1969-1970 (Folder 13: 7)
  - Kiessling, Ed and sons, 1982-1986 (Folder 13: 8)
  - Kim, Sung Bok, 1985 (Folder 13: 9)
  - Kindt, Werner and Werner Montag, 1972 (Folder 13: 10)
  - King, J. Charles, 1981-1993 (Folder 13: 11)
  - King, John, 1982 (Folder 13: 12)
  - Kingston, Thomas S., 1991 (Folder 13: 13)
  - Kirby, John B., 1981-1984 (Folder 13: 14)
  - Kirk, Russell, 1958-1995 (Folder 13: 15)
  - Kirkendall, Richard S., 1970 (Folder 13: 16)
  - Kitzinger, J., 1957 (Folder 13: 17)
  - Klaus(?), undated (Folder 13: 18)
  - Klein, Wayne, 1970 (Folder 13: 19)
  - Kleinfeld, Gerald R., 1981 (Folder 13: 20)
  - Knutson, Joseph L., 1971 (Folder 13: 21)
  - Kockeissen, Joseph E., 1975 (Folder 13: 22)
  - Koller, Kerry, 1989 (Folder 13: 23)
  - Komives, John L., 1969 (Folder 13: 24)
  - Kondelik, John P., 1993 (Folder 13: 25)
  - Kort, Fred, 1971 (Folder 13: 26)
  - Korte, Willi A., 1982-1983 (Folder 13: 27)
  - Kosann, Marci, 1969 (Folder 13: 28)
  - Koslowski, Peter, 1991 (Folder 13: 29)
  - Kotkas, L. J., 1980(?) (Folder 13: 30)
  - Kraditor, Aileen S., 1979-1981 (Folder 13: 31)
  - Kristol, Irving, 1971-1980 (Folder 13: 32)
  - Krukones, James, 1971 (Folder 13: 33)
  - Kselman, Claudia, 1980-1981 and undated (Folder 13: 34)
  - Kselman, Tom, 1979 (Folder 13: 35)
  - Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Erik von, 1982 (Folder 13: 36)
  - Kuh, Richard H., 1970 (Folder 13: 37)
  - Kulbicki, Melvin A., 1980 (Folder 13: 38)
  - Kunich, Michael, 1972 (Folder 13: 39)
  - Kyte, George, 1985 (Folder 13: 40)
  - Lacour, Henry J., Jr., Mr. and Mrs., 1971 (Folder 13: 41)
  - Lalley, J. M., 1965-1978 (Folder 13: 42)
  - Landes, David S., 1987 (Folder 13: 43)
  - Lapeyrouse, Stephen, 1985 (Folder 13: 44)
  - Lapping, Mark B., 1970 (Folder 13: 45)
  - Larmay, Fred N., 1970 (Folder 13: 46)
  - LaRocca, John, 1986 (Folder 13: 47)
  - Larson, B. E., 1970 (Folder 13: 48)
  - Lassner, Franz G., 1979 (Folder 13: 49)
  - Lauber, Jean K., 1979 (Folder 13: 50)
  - Laughlin, Richard W., 1970 (Folder 13: 51)
  - Layle, H. F., 1970 (Folder 13: 52)
  - Lebrun, Richard, 1966-1971 (Folder 13: 53)
  - Lederman, Martin J., 1970 (Folder 13: 54)
  - Lefever, Ernest W., 1981 (Folder 13: 55)
  - Leffler, Phyllis K., 1986 (Folder 13: 56)
  - Lefkovitz, Elliot, 1970-1973 (Folder 13: 57)
  - Lehman, John F., Jr., 1965 (Folder 13: 58)
  - Lemble, George P., undated (Folder 13: 59)
  - Lenski, Gerhard, 1968 (Folder 13: 60)
  - Lepine, Catherine, 1983 (Folder 13: 61)
  - Levant, Howard, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Levine, Daniel, 1989 (Folder 14: 2)
  - Levine, Donald N., 1985 (Folder 14: 3)
  - Levy, Leonard W., 1984 (Folder 14: 4)
  - Levy, Roger, 1971 (Folder 14: 5)
  - Lewis, Marshall C., 1974 (Folder 14: 6)
  - Lewis, Phillip A., 1970 (Folder 14: 7)
  - Lewitz, Lester, Mrs., 1970 (Folder 14: 8)
  - Liddell(?), Charlotte, Mrs., 1982 (Folder 14: 9)
  - Liebman, Marvin, 1987 (Folder 14: 10)
  - Liggio, Leonard P., 1972-1986 (Folder 14: 11)
  - Lincer(?), Dotti, 1996 (Folder 14: 12)
  - Lind, William S., 1971 (Folder 14: 13)
  - Lindley, Robert, 1970 (Folder 14: 14)
  - Lindner, Rudi Paul, 1986 (Folder 14: 15)
  - Lips, David A., 1991-1992 (Folder 14: 16)
  - Lipset, Seymour Martin, 1973-1975. (Folder 14: 17)
  - Lipsett, Don, 1959-1993 (Folder 14: 18)
  - Lit, Theodore, 1964 (Folder 14: 19)
  - Littlejohn, Edward, 1981 (Folder 14: 20)
  - Littmann, Ulrich, 1968 (Folder 14: 21)
  - Livesay, Harold C., 1985 (Folder 14: 22)
  - Locicero, Scott, 1985 (Folder 14: 23)
  - Locke, Mervyn, 1980 (Folder 14: 24)
  - Lockhart, Paul A., Jr., 1981 (Folder 14: 25)
  - Lodge, Ellerton A., 1970 (Folder 14: 26)
  - Loescher, Samuel M., 1981 (Folder 14: 27)
  - Loewenheim, Francis L., 1973-1974 (Folder 14: 28)
  - Lofton, John D., Jr., 1969-1989 (Folder 14: 29)
  - Longmans, Green and Company Ltd., 1951 (Folder 14: 30)
  - Looker, Mark, undated (Folder 14: 31)
  - Losh, Mark S., 1983 (Folder 14: 32)
  - Lougee, Carolyn, 1985 (Folder 14: 33)
  - Lowens, Irving, 1961 (Folder 14: 34)
  - Lubienski, Ricardo J., 1959 (Folder 14: 35)
  - Lucas, Paul, 1972 (Folder 14: 36)
  - Ludwig von Mises Institute, 1990 (Folder 14: 37)
  - Lulves, John F., Jr., 1966-1991 (Folder 14: 38)
  - Lummus, Bertrand W., 1974 (Folder 14: 39)
  - Lundin, Jon, 1967-1970 (Folder 14: 40)
  - Lunsford, Robert D., 1986 (Folder 14: 41)
  - Lux et Veritas, Inc., 1971 (Folder 14: 42)
  - Lynch, K., Mr. and Mrs., 1986 (Folder 14: 43)
  - Lynch, Kevin, 1981 (Folder 14: 44)
  - Lynn, John S., 1972 (Folder 14: 45)
  - Lynn, Robert Wood, 1986 (Folder 14: 46)
  - Lyons, David P., undated (Folder 14: 47)
  - Mable, Phyllis, 1970 (Folder 14: 48)
  - McCaffrey, Neil, 1965-1972 (Folder 14: 49)
  - McCahery, Joseph A., 1978-1984 (Folder 14: 50)
  - McCarter, Neely D., 1984 (Folder 14: 51)
  - McCarthy, Margaret E., 1996 and undated (Folder 14: 52)
  - McCarty, John T., 1970 (Folder 14: 53)
  - McCarty, Peter O., 1984 (Folder 14: 54)
  - McClellan, James, 1967 (Folder 14: 55)
  - McCloud, Neal, 1974-1976 (Folder 14: 56)
  - McConagha, Glenn L., 1969-1994 (Folder 14: 57)
  - McConnell, J., Mrs., 1970 (Folder 14: 58)
  - McCormack, William D., 1987 (Folder 14: 59)
  - McCoy, Ron, 1968 (Folder 14: 60)
  - McCracken, Paul W., 1969-1997. (Folder 14: 61)
    Includes letter to Anthony Sullivan
  - MacDonald, Angus, 1970-1996 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - MacDonald, Malcolm M., 1974 (Folder 15: 2)
  - McDonald, W. Wesley, 1981-1982 (Folder 15: 3)
  - McDowell, Edwin, 1970 (Folder 15: 4)
  - McGarry, Georia, 1985 (Folder 15: 5)
  - McGee, Paul B., undated (Folder 15: 6)
  - McGonagle, David J., 1986 (Folder 15: 7)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1969 (Folder 15: 8)
  - Machan, Tibor E., 1974 (Folder 15: 9)
  - McInerny, Ralph, 1992-1993 (Folder 15: 10)
  - McIntosh, Lester A., 1970 (Folder 15: 11)
  - McIntosh, Tom, 1971 (Folder 15: 12)
  - Mackay, Frank J., 1970 (Folder 15: 13)
  - Mackie, Ethel P., 1964 (Folder 15: 14)
  - McKie, James W., 1975 (Folder 15: 15)
  - Mackinnon, Marianne, 1980 and undated (Folder 15: 16)
  - McLeod, A. Neil, 1986 (Folder 15: 17)
  - Macleod, David, 1986 (Folder 15: 18)
  - McMaster University, 1987 (Folder 15: 19)
  - Macmillan Company, 1966-1968 (Folder 15: 20)
  - McNamara, Joseph S., 1982 (Folder 15: 21)
  - Maddy, Joseph E., 1965 (Folder 15: 22)
  - Madsen, David, 1970 (Folder 15: 23)
  - Maehl, William H., Jr., 1970 (Folder 15: 24)
  - Maggioni, Luigi, 1984 (Folder 15: 25)
  - Maibach, Michael C., 1983 (Folder 15: 26)
  - Mairs, James L., 1970 (Folder 15: 27)
  - Maitre, Von H. Joachim, 1975-1984 and undated (Folder 15: 28)
  - Mall, Loren, 1986 (Folder 15: 29)
  - Manfred, Ernest F., 1969 (Folder 15: 30)
  - Mann, Herbert F., 1973 (Folder 15: 31)
  - Mann, Paul, 1971 (Folder 15: 32)
  - Mann, Robert W., 1969-1984 (Folder 15: 33)
  - Manne, Henry G., 1970 (Folder 15: 34)
  - Manning, Jerry, 1970. (Folder 15: 35)
    Includes printed copy of an article, "Campus Turmoil" by Stephen Tonsor, Sunday News. 1970 and undated
  - Manning, Roger B., 1985 (Folder 15: 36)
  - Manning, Roy O., 1972 (Folder 15: 37)
  - Mantz, Francis M., undated (Folder 15: 38)
  - Marciniak, Edward, 1970 (Folder 15: 39)
  - Marder, Arthur, 1966 (Folder 15: 40)
  - Markovic, Mihailo, 1970 (Folder 15: 41)
  - Marlais, Michael, 1982-1984 (Folder 15: 42)
  - Marmaduke, Arthur S., 1970-1971 (Folder 15: 43)
  - Marsh, Peter T., 1972-1974 (Folder 15: 44)
  - Marshall, J. Paxton, 1971 (Folder 15: 45)
  - Martin, George B., 1992 (Folder 15: 46)
  - Martin, Michael C., 1981-1991 and undated (Folder 15: 47)
  - Marx, Leo, 1975-1976 (Folder 15: 48)
  - Mason, Philip P., 1961 (Folder 15: 49)
  - Massey, Marilyn Chapin, 1986 (Folder 15: 50)
  - Masu(?) Tom, undated (Folder 15: 51)
  - Mates, Michael, 1981 (Folder 15: 52)
  - Mather, Judson, 1965-1971 (Folder 15: 53)
  - Mauro, Tom, 1993-1994 (Folder 15: 54)
  - Mavrodes, Grorge I., 1988 (Folder 15: 55)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1971, Edwin, 1970 (Folder 15: 56)
  - Meisel, J. H., 1971-1996 and undated (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Men's Club, 1970 (Folder 16: 2)
  - Mercy College of Detroit, 1985 (Folder 16: 3)
  - Meridian Books, 1966 (Folder 16: 4)
  - Mewes, Horst, 1992 (Folder 16: 5)
  - Meyer, Frank S., 1957-1971 and undated (Folder 16: 6)
  - Michigan Academy of Science, Arts, and Letters, 1968 (Folder 16: 7)
  - Miles, Stephen B., 1986 (Folder 16: 8)
  - Milione, E. Victor, 1970-1984. (Folder 16: 9)
    See also Intercollegiate Studies Institute
  - Miller, Donald E., 1969 (Folder 16: 10)
  - Miller, Doris M., 1970 (Folder 16: 11)
  - Miller, Fred D., Jr., 1984-1986 (Folder 16: 12)
  - Miller, Freeman D., 1960 (Folder 16: 13)
  - Miller, Maxine and Ed, 1984 and undated (Folder 16: 14)
  - Miller, Ray, 1980-1982 (Folder 16: 15)
  - Milosch, Mark S., 1993 (Folder 16: 16)
  - Mitterling, Philip I., 1965 (Folder 16: 17)
  - Modern Age, 1974 (Folder 16: 18)
  - Molesky, Mark, 1990 and undated (Folder 16: 19)
  - Mondigadeh(?), Anusda, 1963 (Folder 16: 20)
  - Monist, 1974 (Folder 16: 21)
  - Montag, W., 1972 (Folder 16: 22)
  - Moore, Charles L., 1969 (Folder 16: 23)
  - Moore, Michael E., undated (Folder 16: 24)
  - Moravcsik, Julius, 1975 (Folder 16: 25)
  - More, Glen L.(?), 1966 (Folder 16: 26)
  - Moreell, Ben, 1968 (Folder 16: 27)
  - Morris, Geoffrey, 1989 (Folder 16: 28)
  - Moses, Dirk, 1993 (Folder 16: 29)
  - Mosher, Mary Lou, 1971 (Folder 16: 30)
  - Mosse, George L., 1969 (Folder 16: 31)
  - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1969-1973 (Folder 16: 32)
  - Mueller, Franz H., 1981-1985 (Folder 16: 33)
  - Muller, Robert, 1967 (Folder 16: 34)
  - Muncy, Raymond, 1968 (Folder 16: 35)
  - Munro, Donald, 1985 (Folder 16: 36)
  - Murphy, Dwight, 1972 (Folder 16: 37)
  - Murphy, Randa, 1980 (Folder 16: 38)
  - Musick, Doug S., 1989 (Folder 16: 39)
  - Myers, Harold H., 1969 (Folder 16: 40)
  - Nash, George H. III, 1970-1974 (Folder 16: 41)
  - Nasser, Barbara, 1983 (Folder 16: 42)
  - National Association of Scholars, 1990 (Folder 16: 43)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1983 (Folder 16: 44)
  - Nayenga, Peter, 1970 (Folder 16: 45)
  - Nease, Stephen W., 1970 (Folder 16: 46)
  - Nelson, J. Robert, 1957 (Folder 16: 47)
  - Nelson, Jeffrey M., 1970 (Folder 16: 48)
  - Nelson, Ronald R., 1966-1985 (Folder 16: 49)
  - Neuenschwander, John, 1987 (Folder 16: 50)
  - Neuhausen, Ben, 1970 (Folder 16: 51)
  - New American Review, 1977 (Folder 16: 52)
  - New Catholic Encyclopedia, 1966 (Folder 16: 53)
  - New Mexico Quarterly, undated (Folder 16: 54)
  - Newsom, Carroll V., 1969 (Folder 16: 55)
  - New York Times, 1958-1974 (Folder 16: 56)
  - Nichols, Bryan and Darlene, 1986 (Folder 16: 57)
  - Nichols, David C., 1969 (Folder 16: 58)
  - Nichols, James, 1971 (Folder 16: 59)
  - Nichols, Russell L., 1984-1985 (Folder 16: 60)
  - Niemeyer, Gerhart, 1966-1990 (Folder 16: 61)
  - Nimelman, Andrew A., 1985 and undated (Folder 16: 62)
  - Nisbet, Robert A., 1968-1975 (Folder 16: 63)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1969-1981 and undated (Folder 16: 64)
  - Nolan, John G., 1987 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Normack, John, Jr., 1985 (Folder 17: 2)
  - Norman, Warren T., 1971 (Folder 17: 3)
  - North, Gary, 1971 (Folder 17: 4)
  - Northwestern University, 1979 (Folder 17: 5)
  - Northwood Institute, 1979 (Folder 17: 6)
  - Norton, Mary Beth, 1975 (Folder 17: 7)
  - Norton, Stephen, undated (Folder 17: 8)
  - Novak, Michael, 1975-1984 (Folder 17: 9)
  - Noworyta, Timothy J., 1981 (Folder 17: 10)
  - Nurser, John, 1956 (Folder 17: 11)
  - Nutt, Clarence D., 1969 (Folder 17: 12)
  - Nutter, G. Warren, 1966 (Folder 17: 13)
  - Obitts, Stanley, 1970-1972 (Folder 17: 14)
  - O'Brien, Albert C., 1974 (Folder 17: 15)
  - O'Brien, Francis W., 1974-1975 (Folder 17: 16)
  - O'Gorman, Kathy, 1975 (Folder 17: 17)
  - Oklahoma State University, 1974 (Folder 17: 18)
  - Okonski, Raymond N., 1970 (Folder 17: 19)
  - Olasky, Marvin, 1981-1986 (Folder 17: 20)
  - Olegario, Rowena, 1984 (Folder 17: 21)
  - O'Mally, John, 1974 (Folder 17: 22)
  - Opitz, Edmund A., 1970 (Folder 17: 23)
  - Opitz, Peter J., 1975-1980 (Folder 17: 24)
  - Organization of American Historians, 1971 (Folder 17: 25)
  - Ormsby, M. A., 1967 (Folder 17: 26)
  - Orth, Norbert J., 1971 (Folder 17: 27)
  - Ortuno, Manuel, 1970 (Folder 17: 28)
  - Osberger, Alice, 1993 (Folder 17: 29)
  - Oster, Thomas H., 1970 (Folder 17: 30)
  - Overseth, Anneke, 1973 (Folder 17: 31)
  - Ozog, Thaddeus J., 1971 (Folder 17: 32)
  - Pallenger, W. S., 1967 (Folder 17: 33)
  - Panichas, George A.
    - 1980-1989 (Folder 17: 34)
    - 1990-1998 (Folder 17: 35)
  - Parker, Geoffrey, 1990 (Folder 17: 36)
  - Parker, J. A. (Jay), 1970 (Folder 17: 37)
  - Parkes, David G., 1982 (Folder 17: 38)
  - Parsons, Edward, 1985 (Folder 17: 39)
  - Pascol(?), Robert A., 1988 (Folder 17: 40)
  - Paton, William A., 1970 (Folder 17: 41)
  - Patrick, Miriam, 1971-1972 (Folder 17: 42)
  - Patterson, L. G., 1990 (Folder 17: 43)
  - Paul, H. W., 1985 (Folder 17: 44)
  - Payne, Francis Dana, Jr., 1969 (Folder 17: 45)
  - Payzs, Tibor, 1966 (Folder 17: 46)
  - Pearson, Al, 1976-1978 (Folder 17: 47)
  - Pearson, Sidney A., Jr., 1975 and undated (Folder 17: 48)
  - Peckham, Howard H., 1974 (Folder 17: 49)
  - Pejovich, Stefan, 1970-1985 (Folder 17: 50)
  - Pejovich, Svetozar, 1974-1977 (Folder 17: 51)
  - Pells, Richard, 1984 (Folder 17: 52)
  - Penn, Ralph S., 1969 (Folder 17: 53)
  - Pepperdine University, 1980-1982 (Folder 17: 54)
  - Perkins, Bradford, 1971 and undated (Folder 17: 55)
  - Perry, Laurens B., 1965-1968 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Peters, C., 1994 (Folder 18: 2)
  - Philbrook, Clarence E., 1968 (Folder 18: 3)
  - Philipson, Morris, 1977 (Folder 18: 4)
  - Phillips, Clifton J., 1970 (Folder 18: 5)
  - Phillips, Lester H., 1969-1970 (Folder 18: 6)
  - Pickup, Robert E., 1971-1982 (Folder 18: 7)
  - Piekacz, Lucian, 1970 (Folder 18: 8)
  - Pilon, Roger, 1975 and undated (Folder 18: 9)
  - Pitts, Henry L., 1970 (Folder 18: 10)
  - Platt, Michael, 1989-1991 and undated (Folder 18: 11)
  - Podhoretz, Norman, 1974 (Folder 18: 12)
  - Pond, Elizabeth, 1979-1985 and undated (Folder 18: 13)
  - Poppel, Stephen, 1969 (Folder 18: 14)
  - Porter, Clifford F., undated (Folder 18: 15)